<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yihui&#39;s Blog on Yihui Xie | 谢益辉</title>
    <link>https://yihui.name/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yihui&#39;s Blog on Yihui Xie | 谢益辉</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yihui.name/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create GIFs with gifski in knitr Documents</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/gifski-knitr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/gifski-knitr/</guid>
      <description>Last month Jeroen announced the gifski package, which looked pretty cool to me. While thinking about improving the gganimate support in knitr (per Thomas&amp;rsquo;s request), I learned a little more about gifski. The usage seems to be quite straightforward to me, so I wrote a hook function in knitr today to support this package, which means you can easily create a GIF animation from a code chunk now if you have installed gifski, and at least version 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>makeActiveBinding(): The Most Magical Hidden Gem in Base R</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/make-active-binding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/make-active-binding/</guid>
      <description>Of course, this is a follow-up post on my previous follow-up post on lazy evaluation. One commenter (Michael&amp;mdash;I believe I know this Michael) of that post pointed out the function makeActiveBinding() in base R. I have almost forgotten it. It was once the most magical function in my eyes, and was the foundation of one of my only two academic papers, &amp;ldquo;Reactive Programming for Interactive Graphics&amp;rdquo; (Xie et al 2014).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Negatives</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/double-negatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/double-negatives/</guid>
      <description>Every time I use the function stopifnot(...), I have to stop and think about it: should the conditions in ... return TRUE or FALSE? Then I have to think in plain English. Hmm, what does &amp;ldquo;stop if not false&amp;rdquo; mean? Do I actually want to stop or not if the condition is true? All kinds of circles emerging in my mind&amp;hellip;
I have wished many times the function name were stopif() instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on 25&#43; Years of &#34;50 Years of Data Science&#34;</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/25-years-of-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/25-years-of-data-science/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is a guest post and not written by Yihui. Its author desires to remain anonymous. If anyone would like to contact the author, please contact me (Yihui). And if any statistical sleuths out there determine the author&amp;rsquo;s identity, please refrain from revealing it. Thank you.
 When I was a child
I caught a fleeting glimpse
Out of the corner of my eye
I turned to look but it was gone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write a Book with bookdown and Publish with Chapman &amp; Hall</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/bookdown-crc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/en/2018/08/bookdown-crc/</guid>
      <description>My editor John Kimmel told me that many authors showed interest in bookdown at JSM 2018 in Vancouver last week. I was very glad to know that. In this post, I want to briefly explain how to publish a book with Chapman &amp;amp; Hall/CRC. Actually I blogged about it five years ago after I published my first book, but at that time, I was still in the LaTeX (LyX) world, and this time I want to talk about R Markdown instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two of My Use Cases of Lazy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/en/2018/07/lazy-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/en/2018/07/lazy-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>This is a short follow-up post on Colin Fay&amp;rsquo;s follow-up post on Thomas Lumley follow-up post on Miles McBain post about quotation. Yeah, I just cannot help it when I see this streak.
I&amp;rsquo;m not an expert of quotation or lazy evaluation. I just happen to have used them occasionally. I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about two use cases of lazy evaluation.
Executing R code &amp;mdash; the ninja way In two of my talks, I used delayed assignments to execute R code for no good reasons except that I just wanted to confuse the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>