<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TinyTeX on Yihui Xie | 谢益辉</title>
    <link>https://yihui.name/tinytex/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TinyTeX on Yihui Xie | 谢益辉</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yihui.name/tinytex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why TinyTeX?</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/tinytex/pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/tinytex/pain/</guid>
      <description>Some developers may doubt if I&amp;rsquo;m just reinventing wheels. I certainly don&amp;rsquo;t want to reinvent wheels for no reason. As I said on the homepage, my own pain with existing LaTeX distributions is that they are often too big, and the documentation, while being comprehensive and useful, usually does not highlight the most useful part to me (how to find and install a missing package).
I also dislike the fact that it often requires sudo (on *nix) to manage LaTeX packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The R package tinytex</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/tinytex/r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/tinytex/r/</guid>
      <description>You can install the tinytex package from either CRAN or Github:
# CRAN version install.packages(&#39;tinytex&#39;) # or the development version on Github devtools::install_github(&#39;yihui/tinytex&#39;)  The package mainly provides two sets of functions: functions to manage TinyTeX, and those that help compile LaTeX documents to PDF.
Manage TinyTeX The tlmgr_* family of functions calls the TeX Live utility tlmgr to manage TeX Live, e.g., install or update LaTeX packages. See ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TinyTeX 中文文档</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/tinytex/cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/tinytex/cn/</guid>
      <description>TinyTeX 是一个瘦身版的 TeX Live。TeX Live 的庞大体型问题困扰我多年，在 2018 年之前我终于抽出一周时间来解决这个问题，其实方案很简单：把对普通用户毫无用</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently (?) Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://yihui.name/tinytex/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yihui.name/tinytex/faq/</guid>
      <description>TinyTeX is still a relatively new project, so these are only potential FAQs.
 Which version of TeX Live is installed?
The (very) latest. Using the very latest version of a software package can be risky. You have been warned. On the other hand, however, let&amp;rsquo;s not pretend we haven&amp;rsquo;t run into problems using the &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; versions of TeX Live.
Latest or stable? Your call. If you are not comfortable with the latest version, TinyTeX is probably not a good choice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>